



# EDUCATION

### PERSONAL

Name Samuel Svensson Birthday July 10, 1995 Nationality Swedish

Languages Swedish, English, (Spanish)

#### ABOUT ME

I'm a 23 year old Master of Science student that has a passion for creative programming and smart solutions. I've mostly been doing web-development in Javascript but I am always open for opportunities to learn something new. One of my greatest ambitions is to work with 3D-computer graphics and image processing combined with challenging programming assignments!

## CONTACT

Mobile +46 725444332

Email samuel.svensson.95@gmail.com

Address Skomakaregatan 9

602 32 Norrköping

#### LINKS

Portfolio: samuelllsvensson.github.io

Linköping university Norrköping, SE - Master of science in Media technology 2016-Present

Programming, computer graphics, visualization and design.

Selected courses: Course code: Programming (C++) TND012 TNMK30 Electronic publishing TNA003 Object-oriented programmering TNM046 Computer Graphics 3D-Computer Graphics TNM061 Programming in C++ (Continuation course) TNG032 TNM040 Communication and user interfaces Modelling and simulation TNG022 Signals and systems TNG015 Image processing and analysis TNM087

Västerhöjdsgymnasiet (high school) Skövde, SE - Teknikprogrammet 2011-2014 Information and media technology

# **EXPERIENCE**

Norrköping/Linköping, SE Airpelago - Front-end developer 2019/03 - Present

I am soon going to contribute part-time alongside studies to build

a cloud-based ground control station for drone fleet management and operations.

Cygni Norrköping, SE - Student brand manager 2018-Present

I represent Cygni at campus and coordinate events for the students

Linköping university

Norrköping, SE - Teaching assistant 2017/09-2018/01

Assisted younger students in a web development course.

Summer jobs: Engine & AC assembler, warehouseman 2015-2017

#### PROGRAMMING LANGUAGES / SOFTWARE

JAVASCRIPT/REACT/JQUERY, HTML5, CSS3/BOOTSTRAP, C++, GIT, NPM. MATLAB, ADOBE PHONEGAP, ADOBE-SUITE & OFFICE 365. SOME JAVA, PHP AND C# EXPERIENCE.